{
	"category": "History",
	"difficulty": "Intermediate",
	"subcategories": [
		{
			"subcategory": "General History",
			"questions": [
				{
					"question": "What name was given by the French to the combined regions of Nova Scotia and New Brunswick?",
					"answer": ["Acadia"]
				},
				{
					"question": "What great conqueror's body was reportedly preserved in honey after his premature death?",
					"answer": ["Alexander the Great"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Which Canadian statesman was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in 1957 for his efforts to resolve the Suez Crisis?",
					"answer": ["Lester Bowles Pearson", "Lester Pearson", "Pearson"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Considered the 'cradle of civilization', this ancient region of west Asia has what name that refers to its location between the Tigris and Euphrates rivers?",
					"answer": ["Mesopotamia"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Who was the first prime minister of Canada born in the 1900s?",
					"answer": ["Pierre Trudeau", "Trudeau"]
				},
				{
					"question": "What nation's monarch sat on the Peacock Throne until the late 20th century?",
					"answer": ["Iran"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Who commanded the French army at the Battle of Austerlitz?",
					"answer": ["Napoleon", "Napoleon Bonaparte", "Bonaparte"]
				},
				{
					"question": "In what city was the riotous 1968 Democratic National Convention held?",
					"answer": ["Chicago"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Who was Canada's Prime minister during the First World War?",
					"answer": ["Robert Borden", "Borden"]
				},
				{
					"question": "In what year did the Berlin Wall come down?",
					"answer": ["1989"]
				},
				{
					"question": "On May 9, 1955, the Federal Republic of Germany became the fifteenth member of what alliance?",
					"answer": ["NATO", "North Atlantic Treaty Organization"]
				},
				{
					"question": "What was the code name for the Invasion of Normandy?",
					"answer": ["Operation Overlord", "Overlord"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Which German field marshall was known as the 'Desert Fox'?",
					"answer": ["Erwin Rommel", "Rommel"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Who commanded the French Troops who lifted the Siege of Orleans?",
					"answer": ["Joan of Arc"]
				},
				{
					"question": "What collective term was applied to the democratic uprisings in the Middle East that began in 2011?",
					"answer": ["The Arab Spring", "Arab Spring"]
				}
			]
		}
	]
}